# SecureSettings is a PowerShell Module to help you securely keep settings information, like API access keys.
# You use the Add-SecureSetting command to a new secure setting.

# You can store a string:
Add-SecureSetting AStringSetting 'A String' 

# You can store a secure string, which you can ask for with Read-Host -AsSecureString
Add-SecureSetting ASecureStringSetting (Read-Host "Is It Secret?" -AsSecureString)

# You can store a credential, which you can use for access to remote machines.   Prompt for credentials with Get-Credential.
Add-SecureSetting ACredentialSetting (Get-Credential)

# You can even store a complex hashtable (only if it contains strings, numbers, booleans, script blocks, and hashtables)
Add-SecureSetting AHashtableSetting @{
    a='b'
    c='d'
}

# Get-SecureSetting will list settings 
Get-SecureSetting 

# Get-SecureSetting can also list a single one AStringSetting
Get-SecureSetting AStringSetting

# Get-SecureSetting will return results encrypted by default. If you need to access an encrypted result, use -Decrypted
Get-SecureSetting AStringSetting -Decrypted

# Remove-SecureSetting will remove a secure setting.  It supports -WhatIf and -Confirm
Get-SecureSetting | Remove-SecureSetting -WhatIf

# This will clear all settings and prompt.  To avoid the prompt, use -Confirm:$false
Get-SecureSetting | Remove-SecureSetting 